(Sheldon:)you can have your helium
and we'll be on our way.
(Man:)Yeah, well, is there
something wrong with it?
(Leonard:)No, nothing.
We just changed our mind.
(Sheldon:)He has glasses and
I'm a know-it-all;
(Sheldon:)we are not built
for prison.
(Man:)Yeah, I hear you.
(Man:)Well, you're good guys,
so I'll, uh...
(Man:)I'll take the helium
off your hands.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Man:)But you ain't getting
your money back.
(Sheldon:)You're taking advantage of us?
(Sheldon:)We clarified nomenclature
together.
(Man:)Look, I enjoy
semantic digressions
(Man:)as much as the next guy,
but, uh, this is business.
(Leonard:)You know what?
(Leonard:)It's fine.
Keep the money.
(Leonard:)We just want to be
done with this.
(Man:)No problem, but I am
gonna have to charge you
(Man:)a small helium restocking fee.
(Sheldon:)I don't understand.
(Leonard:)He wants more money.
(Sheldon:)Well, it better not be more than
a thousand dollars;
(Sheldon:)that's all I've got on me.
(Man:)That's exactly how much it is.
(Sheldon:)Finally,
(Sheldon:)something breaks our way.